peers asked me
if I thought Jeffrey Epstein was an
Israeli Mossad agent. I said,
"Absolutely, positively yes." And
General Yet, he he sat there like this
the whole show. He just goes
and then Duritz is like, "I object to
that." And constantly interrupting. It's
not my nature to interrupt or if I do, I
apologize for interrupting. Finally,
Pierce told him, "Will you just shut
your mouth and let the man answer the
question?" So, I said, "Look,
the Israelis have always spied on the
United States deeply." I said on my very
first day at the CIA where all the new
hires were sitting in the in the CIA
auditorium called the bubble and we're
getting briefed by like the head of
insurance and the head of this and the
head of that and this is how you fill
out your time card and this is how you
pick your health insurance and and the
head of security came to brief us and um
he said the most important thing that
we're going to need to consider is the
issue of counter intelligence.
There are enemies behind every bush and
they all want to know what we're working
on and what we know about them. We have
to protect ourselves. So he said, "Rule
number one, there's a steakhouse right
down the road. It's the nearest
restaurant to the CIA's headquarters.
Don't ever go in that restaurant." Why?
Because the KGB thinks that we all eat
at that restaurant. So anytime the day
or night, everybody in that restaurant
is a KGB agent
>> waiting for the CIA guy to come in and
who who forgot to take his badge off.
Right.
>> Yeah.
>> Don't ever go in that restaurant.
Secondly, he said
even our friends spy on us.
He said, "Many of you will come into
contact with the two Israeli
intelligence officers who are based at
the Israeli embassy in Washington.
There's a representative from Mossad and
a representative from Shinbet.
He said the FBI has been able to
identify
187 undeclared Israeli Mossad agents
spread all across the United States.
>> Wow.
>> Spying on our defense contractors to
steal our defense secrets. Now, we give
the Israelis 99% of what we have. They
want to steal that last 1%.
>> There's a famous story when we built the
uh F-35.
>> We said to them, "Look, we developed
this new fighter jet. It's stealth. It's
this. It's that. It's amazing.
Everybody's going to get it. It's the
F-35." They said, "We want it." We said,
"Great. We're going to give it to you.
We're going to call it the F-35I for
Israel, and we're going to just very
slightly degrade the avionics." So, God
forbid if it's shot down by the Iranians
or the Syrians or the Russians and they
get the avionics, they won't be able to
duplicate it.
>> They said, "No, we want the F-35 with
with the avionics." We said, "No, no,
okay." So, they're trying to steal the
avionics. At the same time, the UAE came
to us and said, "Hey, we want that
F-35." And we said, "Great. We're going
to give it to you. We're going to call
it the F-35E.
E for Emirates and we're gonna slightly
degrade the avionics. So, god forbid if
the Iranians shoot it down, they can't
get it and reverse engineer it. They
said, "Fine, no problem."
But the Israelis are here to steal the
>> avionics. That's one thing I never was
able to comprehend. I mean, such a
friendly nation
>> who shares intelligence
on
>> constant B. Not not them, us.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes. You're
100% right. Yes.
>> Constantly all the time.
>> Right.
>> And we sell all types of weapons to
Israel and that's why it's such a small
country,
>> right?
>> But yet so powerful,
>> Yeah.
>> Why still try to steal secrets?
>> Why still have these agents, the
Israelis truly believe that they're
alone in the world?
>> Really,
>> they truly believe it.
>> So that's their culture. That's their
psychology.
>> It is. Yes.
>> Trust nobody but themselves.
>> Tell us the story about when the CIA
stopped accepting gifts from from
>> Yeah. When I my my very first liaison
briefing was very early 1990. I was
brand new. I had only been in the CIA
for three or four months and my boss
said, "Hey, you're going to do your
first liaison briefing." Now, when
you're in the director of intelligence,
you're declared to a whole bunch of
foreign intelligence services,
especially when you work on an enemy
country like Iraq, like I did. So, you
know, most people go through their
entire 30-year careers and they're
declared to two or three, four or five
foreign intelligence services where the
CIA says to the head of the other
intelligence service, "This is my guy.
He's a CIA officer." Okay. So, you're
declared. They know you're a CIA officer
because you told them you are. Yeah.
>> Okay.
So, the Israelis would come to
headquarters for their briefings. We we
call them intelligence exchanges
and um they would always bring gifts,
>> right? But the gifts would always have
listening devices embedded in them
>> with batteries. Like they brought this
big seal of the CIA. Oh, we made this
beautiful seal of the CIA as a gift for
you. You should put it in the director's
conference room. and it's completely
embedded with microphones and batteries.
And we're like, "Guys, you you got to
stop doing this. You can't do this." It
got to the point where
>> their response when you like bluntly
say, "Hey,
>> oh well. H you can't blame us for
trying.
It's not funny.
>> There is there's no consequence. There's
like
>> no because then they're going to go to
the Washington Post and say the CIA is
being mean to us."
And then Congress is going to get
involved. say what's the matter with
you? Do you think I mean with certainty
you said Jeffrey Epstein was a massage
agent working here in the US as a
sleeper cell or whatever they call
>> I believe he was an access agent which
is a very specific kind of
>> one director right is that is that what
it means an access agent when you have
one directorate you have to complete
this task
>> no
>> what it means is let's say you're you're
the head of Mossad
>> and you want to know exactly what's
going on in Bill Clinton's mind or
Prince Andrew or Bill Gates or any of
these other people. You're not going to
recruit Bill Clinton. He's not going to
take your money. Yeah.
>> And then report back to you like uh you
know behind the 7-Eleven at 11:00 at
night.
>> So you do the next best thing.
>> You recruit an agent
>> who's friends with Bill Clinton or who
can become friends with Bill Clinton.
>> So you're telling me he wasn't an agent.
He became one. He was recruited to
become an agent. Okay. That's what it
was.
>> So, initially, you know, speaking of
Gelain Maxwell, her dad being a Mossad
agent,
>> I wouldn't be surprised if her dad said
to Mossad, "Listen, my daughter's
friendly with this guy. You might want
to take a look at him."
>> I see.
>> Mhm.
>> And do you think that shapes
uh foreign policy?
>> 100%. Yes. to have these compromise at
this these types of people of you know
this caliber this level
>> and we're not even sure if they have
anything on Trump
>> and that's why Trump just
>> like this attacks Iran without a
question
>> right yep
>> is that a possibility
>> yes
>> okay
>> now Trump will say
that Netanyahu came asked him to bomb
Iran he said no this time Netanyahu
said, "If you don't, we're going to use
nuclear weapons." So Trump did the right
thing. He did the the friendly thing of
bombing them with non-nuclear weapons.
So he actually saved a lot of Iranian
lives. I mean,
>> that's that's what he wants the the
storyline to be. We have no idea what
the truth is.
>> You spoke of conspiracy theorists. I
mean, uh,
the recent Charlie Kirk assassination,
do you think in any way, shape, or form
this was planned by, I don't know, a
foreign government or a a group, a deep
state of people to
just make sure his voice is not heard
anymore because he was changing hearts,
minds, and souls. He was changing the
culture of America.
>> It's It's certainly possible. Listen,
I'm the least conspiracy-minded person
that you will encounter.
>> Okay?
>> 99.9%
of the time,
>> what you see is what you get. It
>> really
>> Yeah.
>> There are so many moving parts in a
conspiracy. And and most of these
organizations that we're talking about,
CIA, FBI, MOSSAD, they are such big,
slow, lumbering bureaucracies full of a
lot of stupid people.
>> I mean, I can see they get caught.
>> Yeah, they get caught
that for everything to just hum
perfectly and never be revealed and
nobody ever ever leaks. Could could it
be outside
sources, outside people, you know,
outside entities?
>> It could be a compartmentalized
operation where, you know, so few people
know about the operation that they could
pull it off.
>> What is the one one conspiracy you
believe in?
>> What's the one conspiracy that I believe
in?
I believe that elements of the CIA were
involved in the killing of John Kennedy.
I believe elements of the Israeli
government were involved in the killing
of John Kennedy.
>> Really?
>> I do.
>> Again, the Israelis.
>> Wh what what what which part which
element puts it together?
>> I was waiting for the president to
declassify all of the remaining JFK
documents,
>> right?
>> Yes.
>> He said he did. He didn't. All of it.
Yeah.
>> No, there's still several thousand pages
and I'm told that they point directly at
the Israelis.
>> Really? Mhm.
>> What would be the benefit of of of
>> They had specifically asked Kennedy for
nuclear technology to build a bomb and
he said that he would never give them
nuclear technology to build a bomb.
>> And at the time Kennedy wanted to
inspect Israeli nuclear sites.
>> Exactly.
>> Right.
>> And I mean and we did. We went there. We
inspected it just like we did in in in
Iran. Right.
>> And Iraq both.
>> And and Iraq. Yeah. And uh
>> you put lead seals, you put cameras, you
have spot inspections, the system works.
>> Yeah. And of course, we never found any,
but we all know that Israel
>> has
>> Yeah.
>> numerous nuclear weapons.
>> Yeah. In fact, on that Pierce Morgan
show, um I I told a a little story about
a friend of mine who retired from the
CIA and started writing books, just
pumping out books, one or two a year,
and he's a brilliant writer. And the
books are on these really obscure
foreign policy issues like US relations
with India during the Kennedy
administration or US relations with
Saudi Arabia during the Franklin
Roosevelt administration.
I love them. But he probably sold 10 or
15 copies. Anyway, he he wrote this book
about
the history of nuclear weapons. It was
like a short history of of nuclear
weapons. And we always everything we
write we have to send to the CIA for
clearance by the publications review
board.
>> They sent back his manuscript
>> and it only had three words blacked out.
Israeli nuclear program.
>> That's it. And he said, "It's not our
secret."
Like, we we don't have classification
authority over the Israeli nuclear
program. It's not up to us to protect
the secrecy of Israel's nuclear